SONAM RANI

Subject Expert/Chemistry Teacher

Address: Sector 10, Gurgaon

Mobile: +91-8700846090 Email: sc.212ad@gmail.com

PROFILE

Experienced academic professional with a professionally qualified academic background and a demonstrated commitment to providing standard value-based education centred on NEP and training teams towards desired goals; described as a "take charge" person with exceptional communication and social skills; proficient in speaking multiple languages; use of MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Shorts & Video making)

OBJECTIVE

Driven to give the entirety, I am capable of offering every student, trainee, and the institution across the board. In terms of delivering long-term services, committed and innovative teaching, cutting-edge and accurate information that is transmitted, engaging classroom activities, and attainable professional goals, I envision myself as the best and most accountable asset to those who rely on me in stride and aim to keep it high.

EDUCATION

HTET (Qualified)	2022
TGT & PGT level	
CTET (Qualified)	2019
(Level 1 & 2)	
M.Ed	78% (2019-2021)
Gurugram University	
M.C. (Assalis J.Ch. assistant)	750/ (2015 2017)
M.Sc (AppliedChemistry)	75% (2015-2017)
Amity University	
B.Ed.	73% (2017-2019)
MDU, ROHTAK	7376 (2017-2019)
B.Sc	70% (2012-2015)
MDU, ROHTAK	,
Grade 12	87.6% (2011)
JJP School	
Grade 10	83.6% (2009)
JJP School	, ,

PERSONAL SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

- ❖ Adaptability to any new work environment
- ❖ A skilled communicator with exceptional presentation and compering skills
- Self-motivated to work independently as well as in teams
- ❖ Student- friendly approach to cater better counselling
- Professionalism and personal etiquette
- Proofreading and Editing

WORK EXPERIENCE

- **\Delta** H.O.D of Chemistry in Sri Chaitanya Techno School, Sec-43 from 2019 to till date.
- ❖ Worked as Chemistry Teacher in Narayana-E techno School from 2018 to 2019:

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

- ❖ Teaching innovatively and conducting various activities integrated to enhance speaking, reading, listening and writing skills of students and trainees
- Conducting and coordinating online workshops for teachers of Sri Chaitanya Schools Techno Curriculum for CBSE for two years in the North Zone.
- * Recruiting teachers at Sri Chaitanya for the North Zone.
- ❖ Preparing subject content, study materials, question papers, worksheets and Admission test papers for Sri Chaitanya and Presenting ideas and content through technically aided methods − PPTs, Short Films, Visual Teaching…etc along with the Resource Team of SCTS.

PROFICIENCY IN LANGUAGES

English and Hindi

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name : Sonam Rani Marital Status : Married

D.O.B : 02.08.1994

Nationality: Indian Gender: Female

DECLARATION

Seeking a position for the role of TGT/PGT Chemistry teacher or Coordinator, of your prestigious institution, Ioffer myself for the post as I believe I am eligible and confident enough to give in the best in all concerns.

I, hereby, declare that the information contained herein, is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and I believe and bear the responsibility for everything.

Date	:	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•
Place	:												
Signature	:												

SONAM RANI